MUSTAFA ERYILMAZ

SUMMARY

Software developer with 2 years in professional and 5+ years of self-development. Electrical and Electronics Engineer with a bachelor and master's degree.

Cloud-based or local, I create games with Unity and applications with Flutter. I improve myself by working in remote and freelance jobs such as mobile application development, python-based applications, UI design.

EXPERIENCE

Mobile App Developer, 01/2018 - Current **RaGi Studios**

• I started working on **Flutter and Unity** on mobile app and game development. I opened my own account as "RaGi Studios" on Google Play, installing some of my applications and testing them.

Research Assistant, 11/2020 - 11/2022 Hacettepe University - Ankara, Çankaya

 For 2 years as a research assistant, I worked on the mechanics, hardware and software of automatic optical scanning device that works with deep learning-based algorithms. I set up a computer vision infrastructure that can detect and classify errors on the PCB and constantly updates its training with new visual data in the loop.

Embedded software and hardware engineer, 01/2020 - 09/2020 Kardinero Medical Systems Inc. - Ankara, Çankaya

 I worked on the hardware and embedded software of a remote access, computer aided and portable robotic exercise platform. I completed the hardware and coding of the electronic hardware I developed.

Part-time Electrical and Electronics Engineer, 12/2018 - 06/2019 MS SPECTRAL DEFENSE INDUSTRY INC. - Ankara, Çankaya

• I worked as a part-time embedded software engineer to improve myself and did embedded coding and system tests for various microcontrollers.

Electrical and Electronics Engineer Intern, 07/2018 - 08/2018 ASELSAN A.Ş. - Ankara, Yenimahalle

• I completed my summer internship at ASELSAN.

Intern Electrical and Electronics Engineer, 06/2016 - 09/2017 APAK ENERJİ A.Ş - Ankara, Çankaya

• Worked on SPP (Solar Power Plant) projects; studies on project drawing, calculations, software, material information were made.



CONTACT

05056710953

in linkedin.com/in/mustafa-eryilmaz

≥ mustafaerylmzz@gmail.com

SKILLS

- <u>Programming Languages:</u>
 Dart, Python, Node.js, C#, C++, Java,
 CSS, HTML
- <u>Frameworks:</u> Flutter
- <u>Database:</u> Google Firebase, MySQL, SQL Server
- Operating Systems: Windows, MacOs, Linux, Ubuntu
- Mobile Development
 Android&IOS Development, API design, RESTful API
- <u>Softwares:</u>

VsCode, Unity, Blender, Figma, Android Studio, Trello, STM32CubeMX, Thonny, Solidworks, AutoCAD, MATLAB, Altium

- Microcontrollers and boards: Raspberry Pi, STM32 ARM, FPGA, MSP430, Arduino
- <u>Designing and Programming:</u> Rotary Wing UAV(Drones), 3D Printer

EDUCATION

Master of Science, Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, 2023

Hacettepe University - Ankara

Thesis topic: Design of Automated Optical Inspection

Device Classification of PCB Defects

Deep learning-based project that can autonomously

detect and classify faults on PCB

Bachelor of Science, Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, 2020

Hacettepe University - Ankara

Graduation Project: Swarm Drones

I have set up a swarm drones that can autonomously perform a joint task with communication among themselves. There were 3 active drones in the system and the number could be increased if desired.

PROJECTS

Visual Notes App

It is an application created to manage your notes with pictures. It gives you a quick and simple note-taking experience with images.

<u>Designed by:</u> Flutter, Dart, Google Admob, Figma, VsCode, Android Studio

Visual Notes App (Google Play)

• HU UAV Society App

It is an application created for HU UAV Society members to share projects, trainings, events and special news about the society.

<u>Designed by:</u> Flutter, Dart, Node.js, Google Firebase, VsCode, Android Studio

HU UAV Society App (Google Play)

• Math Puzzle App

It is 2D math game where user answers some math riddles and their questions are updated and added via cloud. It will be published soon.

Designed by: Unity, C#, Google Admob, Figma, VsCode

• Swarm Drones

In the project, a swarm of drones was established that can autonomously perform a common task by communicating among themselves.

<u>Designed by:</u> Python, C++, C#, VsCode, Raspberry Pi, STM32, Solidworks,

Swarm Drones (Youtube)

 Automatic Optical Scanning Device based on Deep Learning

Deep learning-based project that can autonomously detect and classify faults on PCB

<u>Designed by:</u> Python, Qt, VsCode, STM32, Solidworks, Altium

PUBLISHMENTS

 Conference paper - Defect Classification from Electronic Card Images by Deep Learning (2020 28th Signal Processing and Communications Applications Conference (SIU))

PATENTS

 Printer Device with Automatic Printing Apparatus for Flexible Circuit Applications (Publish date: 27.01.2022 · WO2022/019867 · A1)

CERTIFICATIONS

- Driving License B
- UAS-1 License (UAV-1 License)
- CMAS Diving License

REWARDS

• ISIF'20 Istanbul International Invention Fair, Gold Medal

LANGUAGES

Turkish: First Language

English: C1